<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eclipse Vorto</title>
    <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Eclipse Vorto</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>The Eclipse Vorto Project</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Vorto?</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Interaction among different stakeholders via Vorto
 Vorto provides an Eclipse Toolset that allows Device Manufacturers to easily describe device functionality and characteristics as Information Models. These models are managed in a Vorto Repository. Platform Providers provide Code generators that convert these models into device - specific &amp;ldquo;stubs&amp;rdquo; that run on the device and send Information Model compliant messages to the platform-specific IoT Backend. In order to process these messages in the IoT backend, Vorto offers a set of convenient technical components, for example parsers and validators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 10:58:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>To get started with Vorto easily, we are going to show you how you can use the Vorto IoT Tool to describe a simple device that measures distance and integrate it with Eclipse Hono.
Prerequisites  Maven Java 8 Eclipse for DSL Developers Eclipse Vorto Toolset Plugins  Creating a Vorto Project  Open Eclipse and switch to the Vorto Perspective. In the Vorto Model Project Browser, click the + button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/tutorials/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/tutorials/</guid>
      <description>Connecting a GrovePi This tutorial explains how to generate a simple Python application for you GrovePi that sends sensor data to Eclipse Hono using MQTT.
Prerequisites  Python 3.x
 IDEs - for Python: Visual Studio Code with the Python extension
 Paho Python Client
 GrovePi Sensor Kit
  1. Setup your device. In this example Raspberry Pi is used but you can use any device which can run python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 10:58:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/downloads/</guid>
      <description>To create Informations Models, you need to download the Vorto IoT Toolset plugins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 May 2018 10:58:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/community/</guid>
      <description>Mailing List A great way to stay up to date with Vorto activity is to subscribe to the Mailing list provided by Eclipse. Sign up for the mailing list here.
Discussion Forum A general discussion forum can be found here.
Issue Tracker Issues and bugs related to Vorto are tracked with the Github Issue tracking system. If you find any issues, please report them here.
Vorto Wiki Access Vorto wiki here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/release-notes/</guid>
      <description>0.10.0 milestone 3 Fixes and Enhancements
 EU-GDPR Compliance of Vorto Repository, i.e. Export of user-specific Vorto models. Eclipse Hono Generator, supporting the generation of Arduino-, Python- and Java source code. Code Generator Configuration UI. Code Generators that are executed from the Eclipse Vorto Toolset do now provide a configuration UI that allows developers to customize the execution of the generator.  API Changes
 Vorto Code Generators must now implement org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation Python and GrovePi required modules</title>
      <link>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/installation/grovepi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 May 2018 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.eclipse.org/vorto/installation/grovepi/</guid>
      <description> Download and install the latest version of Python 3.x from the official Python website
 Install pip
 Install Visual C++ Build Tools(http://landinghub.visualstudio.com/visual-cpp-build-tools). This is a pre-requisite for installing netifaces.
 Install the required Python modules
 Eclipse paho netinterfaces
 open terminal or console and type the following command
pip install paho-mqtt pip install netifaces     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>